

# KEITH BROWN

SOFTWARE ENGINEER | 7 ADRIANNE CT, RANDALLSTOWN, MD 21133

## **SKILLS**

Javascript/ReactJs/VueJs AWS Services Drupal CMS Podman/Docker HTML/CSS SQL .Net/Visual Basic NPM/Node Adobe Suite Visual Studio API based development

## **PROJECTS**

#### DRUPAL WEBSITE MIGRATION, 2022, LEADERBANK

Migrated the website for leaderbank from wordpress CMS to drupal. The drupal CMS solution
provided more customizable content solutions for the marketing team. The migration also
improved customer experience by providing a better UI flow and a more modern look and feel
by using Vuejs to create components.

#### SHUTTLE TRACKER, 2019, ERICKSON LIVING

Developed a web based application designed to provide a live GPS tracking update of a
transport Shuttle's position on multiple campuses directly to the web browser using API's from
Google Maps and Amazon Web Services MQTT connections with programming languages
such as Javascript, SQL and HTML. This application is to currently be used by Erickson Living
at over 20 different retirement communities for residents and employees across the US.

# **WORK HISTORY**

### SOFTWARE DEVELOPER • LEADER BANK • DEC 2022 - PRESENT

- Maintain, update, and create content solutions for Leader Bank's website using Drupal CMS and VueIS.
- Used AI solution to evaluate website projects being onboarded from contractors to ensure ADA compliance.
- Rebuilt Vuejs micro apps & components to be compliant and industry best practice.
- Created micro-sites and micro-apps using drupal, AWS solutions, and VueJs.
- Created solutions to help visualize progress of back end processes and provide to stakeholders.







- Created ticketing solution to help standardize workflow across all departments.
- Standardized container creation process as well as upgrade process for drupal CMS. (Podman & Docker containers)
- Created customized logging for drupal environment to catch errors using php.
- Provide updates on assigned projects daily during SCRUM meetings.
- Communicate with product owners to provide revisions & feedback on projects.

#### SOFTWARE ENGINEER • MOSAIC LEARNING • FEB 2020 - AUG 2022

- Maintain, update, and troubleshoot ReactJS framework used across projects to ensure compatibility with other systems both external and internal such as Learning Management Systems (LMS).
- Create custom online learning courses using ReactJS, HTML, & CSS.
- Provide updates on assigned projects daily during SCRUM meetings.
- Communicate with product owners to provide revisions & feedback on projects.
- Create and update Central Management Systems (CMS) for client use.
- Update Jira tickets assigned with current state and progress.

#### SERVICE DESK ANALYST • ERICKSON LIVING • MAR 2019 - FEB 2020

- Applied solutions for projects by using JavaScript/ReactJS, SQL and HTML/CSS as well as integrating and using API's from AWS Services, GoogleMaps API and Salesforce to create web-based applications to support the current working environment.
- Support everyday Tier I and Tier II help desk duties including Answering phones, assisting
  users & residents with a multitude of applications such as MyUnity/Vision, Cisco Phones,
  Simphony, AMAG Badge Management System, AdminWeb/Odessy, EclinicalWorks and some
  support for the SalesForce.com platform.
- Provide phone technical support for Windows 10 and Microsoft Office applications including Outlook & Exchange, Word, Excel and remainder of the Office suite.
- Provide remote technical support using Windows Remote Service Administration Tools.

### HELPDESK ANALYST • PW MEDIA • MAY 2016 - MAR 2019

- Testing and debugging updates made or pending in test environments for website launches prior to creating releases for live environments.
- Create data reports from Google Adwords services to be provided to clients or for internal use for analysis on ad campaigns.
- Support everyday Tier I help desk duties: Answering phones, assisting with website update requests, tracking number routing, and providing general information.
- Support everyday Tier II help desk duties that require updates to MSSQL Database & Central Management System as well as website creation.
- Fix hardware in the work environment such as printers, monitors, desktop towers, etc. when requested.
- Set up networks and workstations for the work environment. Create rj45 cables and sockets, run Ethernet cables throughout the building, set/organize audio and video equipment when requested.

#### CUSTOMER SERVICE • KOHL'S • AUG 2015 - AUG 2016

• Customer service representative at the front desk. Assisted with solving customer issues as presented.







- Worked as a ship from store/stockroom associate while keeping track of inventory of items in the stockroom. Online orders were received in the shipping bay and once completed they mailed to customers.
- Assisted customers in POS and in on Sales floor. Helped customers find items on the sales floor and then proceeded to assist them with checking out of the store to purchase their items.

#### VIDEO GAME COACH • ROLLING VIDEO GAMES • MAY 2014 - JAN 2015

- Worked as a game coach for children in a mobile environment. Customers were provided with video games to play and given assistance where needed.
- Serviced equipment as needed such as repairing game systems, televisions, and components.

# **EDUCATION/CERTIFICATIONS**

#### COMPUTER INFORMATION SYSTEMS • STEVENSON UNIVERSITY • DEC 2018

- Bachelor of Science in Computer Information Systems with a primary focus on Software
  Design. Studied basic programming skills with languages such as C#, Java, Visual Basic/.Net,
  and SQL.
- HDI Support Center Analyst (HDI-SCA) APR 2019

# **REFERENCES**

WENDY PEER,

Vice President, PW Media wendy@pwmedia.com 443-270-4352

Anthony Conklin
Manager at Mosaic
Learning
5126445280
conklin.anthony@gmai
l.com

Ali Osborn Manager at Lovesac 303-579-4625 aliosborn@lovesac.com





